TAYONA JENKINS

TaYonaJenkins1@gmail.com (469)777-0237

SUMMARY

I'm a Recent High School Graduate, currently seeking part-time/full-time employment. I have nearly three years of work history/experience working in several industries which include: Retail, Food Servicing, as well as Restaurants. I'm a great candidate for employment because I regularly practice time management, I'm a very organized person, I'm detail oriented. I am determined to get the job done.

SKILLS

Cashier and Financial Transaction Customer Service and Support Effective Communication Food Service Inventory and Stocking Integrity and Honesty

EXPERIENCE

Kroger's, 235 E. FM 1382, Cedar Hill, TX 75104 Courtesy Clerk, Part-time 20 hrs. per week

05/2019 - Present

- Provide store and product information to customers, assisted with concerns, and worked to resolve customer concerns, compliant, or other important input.
- Deliver warm and friendly greeting while assistance and supporting customer needs and request.
- Provide personal one-on-one service to help customer locate specific products, answer questions regarding merchandise, and/or offer recommendations.
- Correctly identify and display store product and merchandise.
- Completed multiple financial transactions accurately and efficiently while maintaining positive interaction with customers.
- Maintained a high level of cleanliness, organization, and awareness to assigned sales floor area.

Walmart Supercenter, 951 W Belt Line Rd, Desoto, TX 75115

09/2018 - 04/2019

Sales Associate, Apparel/Electronics, Part-time 25-30 hrs. per week

- Ensured product merchandise were correctly identified, displayed, and priced as required.
- Delivered high level of customer service by providing a warm and friendly greeting.
- Provided high level of merchandise and product information and assisted or resolved customer concerns.
- Ensured all cash handling procedures were followed in accordance store policy and procedures.
- Completed multiple financial transactions accurately and efficiently while maintaining positive interaction with customers.
- Maintained a high level of cleanliness, organization, and awareness to assigned sales floor area.

Whataburger, 2965 Dallas Hwy, Waxahachie, TX 75165

04/2018 - 09/2018

Cashier, Food Prep, Part-time 20hrs. per week

- Preformed cash and other financial transactions accurately and honestly in accordance with policy.
- Provided a high quality of service to customers upon arrive and departure.
- Effectively communicated with customers to ensure accurate placement of orders.
- Openly communicated with customers to resolve inaccuracies regarding service.
- Maintained a clean and professional work space at all time to ensure the safety and security of everyone.
- Stocked and replaced inventory, maintained accurate count of supplies and other store goods.

Volunteer Work:

Dept. of Veteran Affairs Medical Center, Vet Center, Dallas, TX

03/2018 - Present

Volunteer, 20-30 hrs. per week

- Distributed information, material, and other resources to Veterans and family members during visit.
- Preformed clerical and other admin duties such as filing, scanning, and uploading documents.
- Greeted Veterans and employees with warm and friendly smile
- Answered multiple phone lines.
- Schedule, changed, and canceled appointments and reminders,
- Maintained registration, sign-in, and visitor logs.

EDUCATION

Cedar Hill High School, Cedar Hill, TX

08/2015 - 05/2019

- High School Graduate, Diploma 05/2019
- GPA: 3.5
- Honor Roll Student,
- Cedar Hill, Texas

CERTIFICATION

- Texas Food Handler's certification (2019-2021)
- Proficient in Microsoft Systems